What's wrong, Xiaobei?
I'm fine.
I'm heading out for a bit.
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
Eat first, then go.
Zhang Xiaobei.
What are you doing here?
Come with me somewhere.
Let's go.
In the middle of the night?
Why'd you bring me to your place?
I've got something to give you.
What is it?
Just five minutes.
You'll love it. Come on!
Zhang Xiaobei, why are you here?
Looks like once it's past midnight,
you switch back right away.
I...
brought Sheng Yuanzhou home.
Now that he's back,
I'll get going.
What?
Father.
Don't call me Father.
I don't need a useless son.
Xiaobei!
The sun is already high in the sky!
You're still sleeping?
Hurry down for breakfast.
Coming.
Coming, coming!
Xiaobei's up!
Come down, come down!
Your mom made you scallion pancakes.
They smell amazing.
Come on, come on!
What's with him?
Here, try some.
Dad, Mom.
I'm finally back.
Eat.
Why is it so greasy?
I used less oil on purpose today.
Mom.
How about we eat out tonight?
No.
Why waste that money?
I already bought groceries for dinner.
It won't cost much.
Mom.
I can earn my own money.
I'll give you a good life.
Hang on.
This kid...
Son...
Where'd you get all this money?
Xiaobei, we're poor, but
you must never do anything illegal.
Mom, I earned this fair and square.
Let's go have a big feast tonight.
Something nice.
Son...
You've worked so hard all these years.
I know you're a good son.
But save the money.
Keep it for Siqi.
Siqi is a good girl.
I'm used to this hard life.
Go wait inside.
I've still got two dishes to make.
Go on.
I heard you mortgaged the land
your mother left you.
I...
Why did you mortgage it?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I'll get it back immediately.
Didn't your panic disorder get better?
Make time to see Dr. Chen.
Yes, Father.
You useless thing.
What's wrong with me?
I mortgaged Mom's land
to buy Zhang Xiaobei's family a house.
None of this sounds like something I'd do.
And...
why did I buy these socks?
Who was I buying them for?
Mr. Sheng.
Why don't you talk to Dr. Chen?
No. If I tell Dr. Chen,
she'll think I'm like my mom,
completely crazy.
Jiang Lai.
Sheng Yuanzhou.
What are you doing here?
Didn't expect you to actually switch back.
What did you say?
I said, "Long time no see."
Get to the point.
Otherwise, leave.
You can't just walk into the Sheng family.
Is that so?
As the Sheng family's future daughter-in-law,
I can't come see
my husband-to-be?
What?
I hereby officially announce
my engagement to Miss Jiang Lai.
How could I be engaged to her?
Honey.
Remember now?
Jiang Lai, listen to me.
I don't know what you did
to make me agree to this engagement,
but I'll never marry you.
Last time, you took advantage of me being drunk,
pretended you slept with me,
and blackmailed me with photos. Forgot?
Do you think I'm that easy to manipulate?
You were cuter back in Commoners' Alley.
I'm leaving.
One more thing.
I wasn't planning to marry you either.
What is she even talking about?
Mom!
Let me help you.
What's gotten into you today?
Before, when I asked you to help,
you couldn't be bothered.
Today you're so eager.
Tell me the truth.
Did you do something you feel guilty about?
No, what is there to feel guilty about?
I just feel like...
you and Dad, for this family,
have had it too hard.
and I haven't been able to do much for you.
As long as you're healthy and happy,
your dad and I will be satisfied.
You don't have to do anything.
Xiaobei, is this your friend?
Mom, go upstairs first.
I'll just talk to her for a minute.
Okay.
Mom, these clothes are all clean.
Just rinse them once more.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I didn't expect
you to actually switch back.
I told you.
I'd only be Sheng Yuanzhou for 30 days.
Today is your Zero Day.
Starting at midnight,
you'll go back to your original identity.
But if, within 24 hours,
you use the Key of Fate to dine with the Sheng family,
you can switch back to being Sheng Yuanzhou.
I've already spoken to my contact in the Sheng family,
and given her a heads-up.
She'll have food ready for you in the kitchen.
Go in through the back door.
Just finish eating in the kitchen.
No need.
Why?
Because I've already avenged my sister.
And I sent Zhu Zipeng to prison.
And I let Sheng Yuanzhou and Lin Siqi
smoothly end their engagement.
And the relocation mess is over now.
So why would I go back to being Sheng Yuanzhou?
I don't believe it.
After living the Sheng family life,
you can still come back to a slum like this.
I want to stay with my family.
To share their hardships.
Your family doesn't need your company.
They need you to give them money,
and give them a better life.
You should treasure the chance to be Sheng Yuanzhou.
That's the only way you can turn things around for them.
If you go back to being broke Zhang Xiaobei,
back to this ant-like existence,
you won't be able to do anything.
You can't help your family at all.
What's the benefit of being Sheng Yuanzhou again?
All the money
is controlled by Sheng Shizhong.
Even when I tried to buy my parents a home,
he had it returned.
So what do my parents actually get out of it?
True.
Right now, Sheng Yuanzhou is still too weak.
There's no way for you to take control of
the Shengshi Group's wealth.
But if you become Sheng Yuanzhou again, you still have a chance.
As long as you stay in Sheng Yuanzhou's place,
I can help your parents unconditionally.
I can get them a new home,
find them a shop to do business,
and give them a sum of money.
I can buy you time
to become someone who can go up against Sheng Shizhong.
You're already Sheng Yuanzhou's fiancee now.
And Sheng Shizhong trusts you, too.
Why are you so fixated on me?
Don't tell me you actually like me.
In my world, there's no romance.
I just think we're alike.
We both know exactly what we want.
Jiang Lai, I'm not like you.
Not at all.
Family and kinship
matter way more to me than money.
After my experiences this past month,
I understand even more how precious love and family are.
So I hope your high road is smooth.
But I'm taking my narrow path.
I don't believe this is your final choice.
I get it.
You want a one-day trip back home.
But friendly reminder:
you've only got 16 hours left.
Who are you?
You mortgaged the land your mother left you.
I...
Zhang Xiaobei.
Sheng Yuanzhou.
Come in.
Father, you wanted to see me?
Come on.
You're coming with me to take care of something.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Don't throw that away!
What are you doing?
Xiaobei, your dad wasn't home,
so they rushed right in.
Sheng Yuanzhou.
Today's the final deadline to move.
But your relocation compensation hasn't arrived yet.
Do you never go online?
It's already been debunked online.
That video is suspected to be fake.
So we've canceled the extra compensation.
You have to move out today.
Do you really have to take it this far?
Business is business.
Chairman Sheng Shizhong,
you're already very rich.
Why can't you just spare people like us?
The things in our home, to you,
are just pocket change.
Money is money.
There's no big or small.
You're just greedy.
I respect money.
But you don't deserve respect.
Then that "respect" you talk about
can it get you out of this predicament?
This world itself is
a jungle where the strong prey on the weak.
There's only so much money.
If you want more in your own pocket,
you have to snatch it from someone else's.
The essence of survival
is slaughter.
I'll leave you with one last piece of advice.
If you don't want to be stepped on,
then step on others first.
If you go back to being broke Zhang Xiaobei,
you won't be able to do anything.
You can't help your family at all.
Siqi.
Xiaobei, what are you doing here?
You've worked hard taking care of Uncle these days.
I just heard the nurse say
Uncle's been pretty stable lately.
How about we go on a date today?
But aren't we...
Come on.
You like it? I bought it just for you.
Xiaobei.
Why did you suddenly come back again?
Why is it that sometimes
it feels like you've become someone else,
like you're two different people?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
They've got the ice cream you like over there.
Want some?
Let's go.
Hello
One strawberry with chocolate syrup,
and some crushed Oreos.
Thanks
Okay
Why does it feel like that familiar Zhang Xiaobei
is back again
Your ice cream
Thank you
Here
If it could stay like this
that'd be great